<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explorer</string>
    <string name="munnar">Munnar is a town in the Western Ghats mountain range in
        India’s Kerala state. A hill station and former resort for the British Raj elite,
        it is surrounded by rolling hills dotted with tea plantations established in the
        late 19th century. Eravikulam National Park, a habitat for the endangered mountain
        goat Nilgiri tahr, is home to the Lakkam Waterfalls, hiking trails and 2,695m-tall
        Anamudi Peak.Most of the native flora and fauna of Munnar have disappeared due to
        severe habitat fragmentation resultant from the creation of the plantations.
        However, some species continue to survive and thrive in several protected areas
        nearby, including the new Kurinjimala Sanctuary to the east, the Chinnar Wildlife
        Sanctuary, Manjampatti Valley and the Amaravati reserve forest of Indira Gandhi Wildlife
        Sanctuary to the north east, the Eravikulam National Park and Anamudi Shola National Park
        to the north, the Pampadum Shola National Park to the south and the proposed Palani Hills
        National Park to the east.</string>
    <string name="linkmunnar"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Munnar">More Info</a>
    </string>
    <string name="vagamon">Vagamon, also spelt Wagamon, is a hill station located in Meenachil
        taluk and Kanjirappally taluk of Kottayam district and Peerumade taluk of Idukki district
        of the state of Kerala, India. Vagamon was discovered by the British who found the place
        ideal for tea plantations and they were followed by Christian missionaries who built their
        abode of service at Kurisumala in Vagamon. National Geographic Traveler has listed Vagamon
        on their directory of the "50 most attractive places to visit in India". Still untouched
        by commercialisation, the sleepy town is surrounded by valleys, green meadows, pine
        forests, mists, fogs, tea estates, waterfalls and overall greenery.[citation needed]
        The landscape is mostly hilly bald with green meadows. Vagamon is also home to a variety
        of flowers and orchids. Three hills - Thangal, Murugan and Kurisumala hills - are the
        representation of the chief religions in Kerala, i.e. Hindu, Muslim, and Christian which
        represent the cultural harmony. Vagamon has amenities for trekking, paragliding,
        mountaineering and rock climbing.</string>
    <string name="kochi">Kochi ([koˈtʃːi ] (About this sound listen)), also known as Cochin
        (/ˈkoʊtʃɪn/ KOH-chin), is a major port city on the south-west coast of India bordering
        the Laccadive Sea. It is part of the district of Ernakulam in the state of Kerala and
        is often referred to as Ernakulam. The city has a corporation limit population of
        612,343,[8] and a metropolitan population of 2.1 million, making it the largest urban
        agglomeration in Kerala. Kochi city is also part of the Greater Cochin region[9][10]
        and is classified as a Tier-II city by the Government of India. The civic body that
        governs the city is the Kochi Municipal Corporation, which was constituted in the
        year 1967, and the statutory bodies that oversee its development are the Greater
        Cochin Development Authority[11] (GCDA) and the Goshree Islands Development Authority
        (GIDA).[</string>
    <string name="kottakkunnu">Kottakkunnu, Known as Marine Drive of Malappuram is a hill
        garden. Kottakkunnu park contains an Open Air theater, Lalitha Kala Academy Art gallery,
        a water theme park, Adventure Park, Kids traffic park, Balloon Park, 16D Cinema. There
        is Water fountain and Laser show on every weekends and on festivals like Eid, Onam,
        New year eve etc. At Kottakkunnu one can see traces of the first fort built by the
        Zamorins. This tourism destination turned historic hill attracts lakhs of people per
        annum. This scenic table-top location is located at the crest of the Cantonment Hill
        near the District Collectorate in the heart of Malappuram city and 51 km from Kozhikode,
        12 km from Kottakkal, 25 km from Karipur Airport, 17 km from Angadipuram railway station
        and 29 km from Tirur railway station. Visitors are allowed up to 9pm.
        [clarification needed] KSRTC Bus station located adjacent at Up Hill is the nearest bus
        station.</string>
    <string name="alappuzha">Alappuzha (About this sound pronunciation (help·info)), also known
        as Alleppey, is the administrative headquarters of Alappuzha District of Kerala state
        of southern India. Alappuzha is a city and a municipality in Kerala with an urban
        population of 174,164[1] and third among the districts having highest literacy rate
        in Kerala. In 2016, Centre for Science and Environment rated Alappuzha as the top
        cleanest town in India followed by Mysuru and Panaji[2] Alappuzha is considered to be
        the oldest planned city in this region and the lighthouse built on the coast of the
        city is the first of its kind along the Laccadive Sea coast (reference encyclopaedia of
        Kerala in Malayalam language).</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main11">Main11Activity</string>
</resources>
